http://www.epsu.org/epsu-data-privacy-policy?mefibs-form-autocomplete-search_api_views_fulltext=&mefibs-form-autocomplete-mefibs_block_id=autocomplete

Skip to main content
Forgot your password?
EPSU Data Privacy Policy
The European Federation of Public Services Union (EPSU) complies with the privacy legislation and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
How does EPSU collect personal data?
EPSU only collects personal data that you give us yourself or that third parties give us in the context of a service requested by them (for example a registration form, an application…).
What personal data does EPSU process?
EPSU only collects the personal data needed to carry out a service requested by you (or by a third party).
When and why does EPSU process personal data?
EPSU processes these data in certain situations:
if you have explicitly given your permission for this;
if it is necessary to process the data in order to provide a service you have requested (for example, your address to send a publication or documents for a meeting or for visa request processing, or your bank account number to pay out financial support);
if we are legally obliged to process the data (for example EC projects);
if it is necessary for a legitimate purpose or in the public interest or (for example processing visa requests).
How does EPSU treat personal data?
Sensitive personal data (bank account numbers, ID or passports numbers) are always treated as confidential and never made public.
Your data are only used for the service you have requested - for example, if you subscribe for one or more newsletters, we will only use your details to send you these newsletters. Every newsletter also gives you the opportunity to unsubscribe.
We never pass on your contact details to third parties for commercial purposes.
How long does EPSU  keep personal data?
If you use EPSU website to register for an event, we will only keep your data for the time needed to provide EPSU services (meetings organisation and follow-up, EC projects…)
Does EPSU keep my personal data safe?
Your data are processed safely, we use secure technologies and measures to protect your data from unauthorised access, use, loss or publication. These technologies and measures are tested on a regular basis and updated when necessary.
What can I do about my own personal data?
If you want to view or update any of your contact details, or delete any data, please send us an email at contact-database@epsu.org
You have the right to be ‘forgotten’. To request this, please contact contact-database@epsu.org
If you consider that your data have been handled incorrectly, you can submit a complaint to the Privacy Commission
If you have any further questions or concerns:
